Guide to the Lindbergh Picture Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Topical, 1880-1983; Series VII
  - Places
    - United States
      - Michigan, 1898-1973 (Box 46, Folder 11-17)
        See also: Oversize, box 86, folder 1
      - Minnesota, Circa 1934-1935 (Box 46, Folder 18)
        Aerial views.
        See also: Oversize, box 77, folder 5
      - Minnesota, Circa 1900-1930s (Box 47, Folder 1-8)
      - Missouri, Circa 1920s-1960s (Box 47, Folder 9-11)
      - Montana, Undated, Circa 1960s (Box 47, Folder 12-13)
      - New Jersey, 1890s-1930s (Box 47, Folder 14-17)
      - New York, 1890s-1930s (Box 47, Folder 18-24)
        See also: Oversize, box 77, folder 6
      - Pennsylvania, Circa 1900s-1960s (Box 47, Folder 25)
      - South Carolina, 1930s-1940s (Box 47, Folder 26)
      - Vermont, Undated (Box 47, Folder 27)
      - Virginia, Circa 1907-1915 (Box 48, Folder 1-2)
      - Washington, DC, Circa 1907-1928 (Box 48, Folder 3-10)
        See also: Oversize, box 86, folder 2
      - Wisconsin, University of, 1920-1922 (Box 48, Folder 11)
      - Wyoming (Yellowstone Park), 1922 (Box 48, Folder 12)
      - Virgin Islands, Circa 1940s-1960s (Box 48, Folder 13)
      - Los Angeles to Washington, DC, aerial views, Circa 1920s-1930s (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Unidentified places, Circa 1920s-1960s (Box 48, Folder 15-19)
  - Spirit of St. Louis
    - General, 1927 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Circa 1927 (Box 49, Folder 2)
      Consists of photographs of the plane's interior.
    - Circa 1927 (Box 49, Folder 3)
      Financial backers: Harold M. Bixby, Harry F. Knight, Harry H. Knight, Albert Bond Lambert, J. D. Wooster Lambert, E. Lansing Ray, Mr. Robertson, and Earl C. Thompson.
    - 1927 May (Box 49, Folder 4)
      Log of flight from San Diego to New York.
    - 1927 May 17 (Box 49, Folder 5)
      Weather map.
    - 1927 May 25 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - 1927 May 28 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - 1927 May 31 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - 1927 June 6 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - 1927 July (Box 49, Folder 10)
      In Ottowa.
    - 1927 Sep 21-22 (Box 49, Folder 11)
      Commemorative display in Riverside, California.
    - 1937 October 3 (Box 49, Folder 12)
      Map of transatlantic flight.
    - Circa 1927-1928 (Box 49, Folder 13)
      In Latin America.
    - Circa 1930s-1960s (Box 49, Folder 14)
      At the Smithsonian Institute.
    - Circa 1950s (Box 49, Folder 15)
      Consists of photographs of exhibited transatlantic flight memorabilia.
    - 1953 (Box 49, Folder 16)
      From Evening Post.
    - 1955 (Box 49, Folder 17)
      On set of the movie The Spirit of St. Louis.
    - Circa 1956 (Box 49, Folder 18)
      Replica of plane.
    - Circa 1970 (Box 49, Folder 19)
      Working model of the Spirit of St. Louis with creator, Cornelius Alos.
    - 1974 (Box 49, Folder 20)
      Model plane and map of flight in Switzerland.
    - Circa 1977 (Box 49, Folder 21)
      Replica of plane and commemorative flight.
    - 1983 (Box 49, Folder 22)
      On display at the Smithsonian Institute.
    - Undated (Box 49, Folder 23)
      Spirit of St. Louis replica.
  - Aviation general
    - Adamowicz, Ben and Joseph, 1934 (Box 49, Folder 24)
      Flight from Newfoundland to France.
    - Air Force Academy site, 1957 (Box 49, Folder 25)
    - Airmail, 1926 (Box 49, Folder 26)
    - Airmail Association, Circa 1927 (Box 49, Folder 27)
    - Amundsen polar flight, 1925 (Box 49, Folder 28)
    - Aviation exhibition, unidentified, Circa 1966 (Box 49, Folder 29)
      In Helsingborg, Sweden.
    - Bolling Field, 1928 March 22 (Box 49, Folder 30)
    - Byrd and Noville, 1953 (Box 49, Folder 31)
      With the family that found them after their forced landing.
    - Chamberlain HOP8, 1927 June 4 (Box 49, Folder 32)
    - Civil Air Patrol headquarters, 1956 (Box 49, Folder 33)
    - Columbia Aircraft Corporation (NX237), Circa 1927 (Box 49, Folder 34)
    - Consolidated Aircraft Corporation
      See: Oversize, box 77, folder 8
    - Costes arrival at Le Bourget airport, France, 1927 October 10-1928 April 14 (Box 49, Folder 35)
    - Curtiss airplanes, 1910-1914 (Box 49, Folder 36)
    - Curtiss SBC-3, Circa 1936 (Box 49, Folder 37)
    - Fighter airplane, Circa 1940s (Box 49, Folder 38)
    - Fowlers hydroplane, Circa 1934 (Box 49, Folder 39)
    - Guynemer, Georges, 1918 (Box 49, Folder 40)
    - Hawks, Frank, Circa 1930 (Box 49, Folder 41)
    - Holger Hoiriis and Otto Hillig, 1931 June (Box 49, Folder 42)
    - Junkers, at Floyd Bennett's grave, 1929 April 28 (Box 49, Folder 43)
    - Lambert Field, 1925 (Box 50, Folder 1-3)
    - Lindbergh Pacemaker, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Lockheed Sirius, 1930s, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Monocoup, 1962, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Moyle, Don, and Cecil Allen, October 1931 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Nichols, Ruth R., 1931 June (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Nungesser, Charles, Circa 1927 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Pan American Airways Clipper, 1929 September (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Pan American Airways crew, 1937 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - "Rangers" flying association, 1966 June (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Roosevelt Field, 1927 May 20 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Ryan Aeronautical Company, 1928 December 15 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Sachem SA3, 1933 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Sikorsky seaplane, 1938 (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Solberg, Thor, 1935 (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - St. Louis air show, 1925-1926 (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - "St. Louis aviation oldtimers", Circa 1963 (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - Transcontinental Air Transport hangar, Circa 1940s (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - Twentieth anniversary of transatlantic flight, 1947 (Box 50, Folder 21)
    - U.S. Commemorative Tour airplanes
      See: Oversize, box 77, folder 9
    - Westover's ship, Undated (Box 50, Folder 22)
    - Wheel wells and instrument panel, Circa 1940s (Box 50, Folder 23)
    - Unidentified airplanes, Circa 1930s (Box 50, Folder 24)
      See also: Oversize, box 77, folder 10
  - Miscellany
    - "Around the North Atlantic" article, Undated (Box 50, Folder 25)
    - Automobiles and motorcycle, Undated (Box 50, Folder 26)
    - Aviation memorials, 1914-1918 (Box 50, Folder 27)
    - Books and writings (Charles August Lindbergh), Circa 1913-1923 (Box 50, Folder 28)
    - Bullfighting, 1924 (Box 50, Folder 29)
    - Commemorative medals and plaques, Undated (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Cranbrook sculptures, Circa 1943 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Houses and buildings
      - Cutter family
        See: Oversize, box 78, folder 1
        Consists of interior views of Grandma Cutter's home in Cleveland, Ohio.
      - Land family, Undated (Box 51, Folder 3)
        In Detroit, Michigan.
      - Morrow family [?], Undated (Box 51, Folder 4)
        See also: Oversize, box 77, folder 11
      - Unidentified, Undated (Box 51, Folder 5)
        See also: Oversize, box 77, folder 12
    - Lindbergh, Elizabeth Lodge Land, motherhood award, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Lindbergh, Elizabeth Lodge Land, 1928 (Box 51, Folder 7)
      Miscellaneous prints collected in Turkey.
    - Moon views (Mt. Wilson observatory), 1919-1925 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Moon and earth views from space (NASA), Circa 1968 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Morrow, Elisabeth Reeve, plaque, 1951 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Parade in Lampasas, Texas, Circa 1974 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Pets, Undated (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Perfusion pump, Circa 1937 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Peruvian whaler, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Prints, general, Undated (Box 51, Folder 15-16)
      Folder 15 includes photograph "Homing pidgeon rising in flight" signed by Harold Edgerton.
    - Responses to Gift from the Sea, Circa 1955-1971 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Russian art, Circa 1938 (Box 51, Folder 18)
      Includes prints and postcards of art and scenes.
    - Statues, Undated (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Trains, Undated (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - Other items related to Charles Augustus Lindbergh and Anne Morrow Lindbergh, Undated (Box 51, Folder 21)
      See also: Oversize, box 77, folder 13
- Graphic art and postcards, 1893-circa 1970s; Series VIII
  The series is arranged by material type and subject, with graphic art listed first followed by postcards.
  The series includes non-photographic graphic depictions of the Lindberghs and Morrows, including drawings, silhouettes, photographs of paintings, and sculpture as well as drawings and paintings by Charles Augustus Lindbergh, Anne Morrow Lindbergh and their children. Additional images include political cartoons related to Charles August Lindbergh and commemorative artwork related to the transatlantic flight. The postcards in the series depict events and locations and were primarily collected by Charles Augustus Lindbergh and his mother Evangeline Lodge Land Lindbergh.
  - Lindbergh, Anne Morrow
    - Bust of, Undated (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Drawings of and by, Undated (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Watercolors by, 1935 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Lindbergh, Charles Augustus
    - Busts of, Circa 1940-1987 (Box 52, Folder 4-9)
    - Drawings of, Circa 1920s-circa 1970 (Box 52, Folder 10-12)
    - Drawings by, Circa 1907, undated (Box 52, Folder 13-14)
    - Monotype of, Circa 1927 (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Painting for, 1932 (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Paintings of, Circa 1927-1970s (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - Sculpture of, Undated (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - Silhouette of, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Stained glass of, Undated (Box 52, Folder 20)
    - Wooden collage of, Undated (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Lindbergh, Charles August
    - Bust of, 1940 (Box 52, Folder 22)
    - Campaign artwork, 1911-1918 (Box 52, Folder 23)
    - Political cartoons, 1910-1923 (Box 52, Folder 24)
      Associated with Charles August Lindbergh's political campaign.
  - Lindbergh, Charles Augustus, Jr. (drawing of), 1932 (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - Lindbergh, Elizabeth Lodge Land
  - Lindbergh, Jon
    See: Oversize, box 82, folder 2
  - Lindbergh, Land Morrow (drawing by), Circa 1940-1945 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    See also: Oversize, box 86, folder 11
  - Morrow family (set of silhouettes), Undated (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Morrow, Dwight Whitney (bust of), Undated (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Morrow, Elizabeth Cutter (painting of), Undated (Box 53, Folder 4)
    See also: Oversize, box 84, folder 1
  - Morrow, Elisabeth Reeve (drawing of), Circa 1931 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    See also: Oversize, box 84, folder 2
  - Spirit of St. Louis (drawings and paintings), Undated (Box 53, Folder 6-7)
    See also: Oversize, box 84, folder 3
  - Transatlantic flight (memorabilia art piece), 1927 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - "First World War Interventionist", Circa 1930s (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Postcards, Circa 1893-circa 1950
    - Chronological (Box 54)
    - Subjects (not geographical) (Box 54)
    - United States (Arizona to California-missions) (Box 54)
    - United States (California-Mt. Lowe to New York-Coney Island) (Box 55)
    - United States (New York-Hudson Valley to Washington DC-Library of Congress, Reynolds series) (Box 56)
    - United States (Washington, DC-Lincoln Memorial) to Egypt (Box 57)
    - France to Turkey (Box 58)
- Motion picture film, Circa 1932-1962; Series IX
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted pending preservation assessment and reformatting.
  - Lindbergh, Charles Augustus
    - "Lindbergh in Mexico", Circca 1930s; 1 (Box 87)
    - "Lindbergh testifies before Senate Post Office Committee", 1934; 1 (Box 88)
    - Untitled, Undated; 1 (Box 89)
  - Lindbergh, Charles Augustus, Jr.
    - "Lindbergh baby", Circa 1930-circa 1932; 1 (Box 90)
    - "C. A. Lindbergh", Circa 1930-circa 1932; 1 (Box 91)
    - "Baby", Circa 1930-circa 1932; 1 (Box 92)
    - "North Haven, Maine", Circa 1930-circa 1932; 1 (Box 93)
  - Lindbergh, Jon Morrow
    - "Baby Jon", Circa 1932-circa 1933; 1 (Box 94)
    - Jon circa one year, Circa 1933; 1 (Box 95)
    - "Jon and dogs, North Haven, summer", Circa 1932-circa 1935; 1 (Box 96)
    - "Thor's tricks", 1933; 1 (Box 97)
    - "Short film of Jon taken at Teton Valley Ranch by M. Wilson", 1943 summer; 1 (Box 98)
  - "North Haven, for Anne", Circa 1930s; 1 (Box 99)
    Preservation issue: film sag.
  - North to the Orient, 1962; 1 (Box 100)
  - Wild Gold, 1958; 1 (Box 101)
- Oversize
  Rolled photographs in box 102 are restricted pending preservation treatment.
  - Lindbergh, Charles Augustus
    - Portraits, 1905, 1926-circa 1940 (Box 59, Folder 1-5)
    - With Charles August Lindbergh and Evangeline Lodge Land Lindbergh, 1907-1912 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - General, Circa 1927-1928 (Box 60, Folder 2)
      Includes a picture of Charles Augustus Lindbergh with Will Rogers.
    - Photographs by Rugh, St. Louis, Missouri, Circa 1927 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Photomontage, Circa 1927 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - With Evangeline Lodge Land Lindbergh, 1927 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Reception in New York, 1927 June 16 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - In Tokyo with Anne Morrow Lindbergh, Circa 1928-1929 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Receiving Congressional medal, 1928 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - First National Aeronautical Safety Conference luncheon, 1928 October 5 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - At Mitchell Field, 1929 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - With Anne Morrow Lindbergh, 1929 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - General, 1929 (Box 60, Folder 11)
      Includes photograph with Amelia Earhart and Mary Pickford.
    - In flight with Anne Morrow Lindbergh, Circa 1930s (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - In Lockheed Sirius, 1930-1931 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Composite photographs of Charles and Anne, the Lockheed Sirius and route map for Pacific and Atlantic surveys, 1931, 1933 (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - In flight, Circa 1931-1936 (Box 60, Folder 15-16)
    - With Hopewell detectives, Circa 1932 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - With M. M. Jensen, Circa 1933 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - With others in boats, Circa 1935 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - The Guild of Air Pilots and Air Navigators of the British Empire, presentation dinner, London, 1936 December 5 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - In India, 1937 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - In uniform, 1939 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - National Advisory Committee for Aeronautics meeting, 1939 October 19 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - With Colonel Frank Borman, Circa 1970 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - in Japan, 1970 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - In Philippines, 1970 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - In Maui, Hawaii, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Albums
      - Boyhood, Circa 1906-1910 (Box 62, Folder 1)
        Includes family members, Washington DC, camping trips, Cass Lake and Lake Ruth.
      - "Pictures taken by my mother and myself in Minnesota, Michigan, Washington, DC and various trips", Circa 1910-1916 (Box 62, Folder 2)
      - St. Thomas and St. Croix, Circa 1928 (Box 63)
        Primarily views but includes a few pictures of Charles Augustus Lindbergh and Evangeline Lodge Land Lindbergh.
      - At Heinkel factory, Germany, 1936 July 27 (Box 64, Folder 1)
      - In Dessau (?), Germany, 1936 July 30 (Box 65, Folder 1)
      - Inspecting Luftwaffe, 1936 July-August (Box 64, Folder 2)
      - Inspecting Luftwaffe, Berlin, 1936 September (Box 64, Folder 3)
      - Germany (portfolio), 1938 (Box 64, Folder 4)
        Includes proclamation and ceremony program.
  - Lindbergh, Anne Morrow
    - Portraits, Circa 1920-1955, 1977 (Box 66, Folder 1-6)
    - School group portraits, Circa 1920-1922 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Atlantic survey flight (?), 1933 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Receiving honorary degree, Middlebury College, 1976 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Lindbergh children
    - Group
      - Charles Augustus Lindbergh, Jr., with Anne Morrow Lindbergh, Elizabeth Cutter Lindbergh and Annie Spencer Cutter (portraits), 1930 (Box 67, Folder 1)
      - Jon Morrow Lindbergh with Anne Morrow Lindbergh, Elizabeth Cutter Morrow and Annie Spencer Cutter (portraits), 1932 (Box 67, Folder 2)
      - Jon Morrow Lindbergh with Anne Morrow Lindbergh, Elizabeth Cutter Morrow and Annie Spencer Cutter (portraits), 1934 (Box 67, Folder 3)
      - Reeve Morrow Lindbergh with Anne Morrow Lindbergh, Jon Morrow Lindbergh, and Elizabeth Cutter Morrow (portraits), 1948 (Box 67, Folder 4)
      - Large contact sheets, Circa 1930s-1940s (Box 67, Folder 5)
        Includes pictures of family at Long Barn and on trips.
      - Negatives (duplicates), Undated (Box 67, Folder 6)
      - Albums
        - Family
          - Volume I, 1935-1936 (Box 68)
            Includes photographs with Dr. Goddard and Guggenheim and rocket experiments in New Mexico. Anne Morrow Lindbergh, Jon Morrow Lindbergh, and Charles Augustus Lindbergh in North Haven, Wales, Long Barn, St. Michel, and France.
          - Volume II, 1936-1937 (Box 69)
            Includes photographs with Dr. Alexis and Mrs. Carrel in St. Gildas, France, their Mohawk airplane in R. Shannon, Ireland, Long Barn. Jon, Anne Morrow Lindbergh, Charles Augustus Lindbergh in Rome, Siciliy, Palestine, Rutba, Iraq, and India.
          - Volume III, 1937 (Box 70)
            Includes photographs of India, Jon Morrow Lindbergh, Anne Morrow Lindbergh, Charles Augustus Lindbergh, Land Morrow Lindbergh and Thor (pet) in Long Barn.
        - Children
          - Volume I, Jon, 1932-1939 (Box 71)
            Includes photographs of Jon Morrow Lindbergh alone and with parents and grandparents.
          - Volume II, Land, Anne, Scott and Reeve, 1937-1949 (Box 72)
            Includes of children individually and with parents.
    - Individual
      - Lindbergh, Charles Augustus, Jr., 1930 (Box 73, Folder 1)
      - Lindbergh, Land, 1947 (Box 73, Folder 2)
      - Lindbergh, Anne Spencer, 1950 (Box 73, Folder 3)
      - Lindbergh, Reeve Morrow, 1948-1951 (Box 73, Folder 4-5)
  - Lindbergh/Land/Lodge families
    - Lindbergh, Evangeline Lodge Land, 1881-1953 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Land, Frank, Fred, Gordon, Scott, Charles Henry, Circa 1860s (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Land, Susan H. (?), Charles Henry, Clara, Scott, and Fred, Circa 1860s (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Land, Charles Henry, Circa 1875-1898 (Box 74, Folder 3)
      Includes portraits.
    - Land, Charles Henry, Jr., Circa 1899-1900 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Land, Evangeline Lodge (portraits), Circa 1900 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Lodge, Edwin Albert, Circa 1850s-1870 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Witherspoon family, Circa 1850s (Box 74, Folder 7)
      Family portrait with Captain John, Roy, John, Arthur, Homer, Emma Lodge, Edwin, Henry, Edith and Emma Bertha.
  - Morrow family
    - Morrow children portrait, Circa 1920 (Box 75, Folder 1)
      With Elizabeth Cutter Morrow, Dwight Morrow, Jr. and Constance Morrow.
    - Morrow, Constance Cutter (portraits), 1937 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Morrow, Dwight Whitney, Sr. (portraits), Circa 1910-1937 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Morrow, Dwight Whitney, Jr. (portraits), 1932 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Morrow, Elizabeth Cutter (portraits), 1920s, 1940 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Morrow, Elizabeth Cutter with grandchildren, 1945-1950 (Box 75, Folder 6-10)
    - Morrow, Elisabeth Reeve (portraits), Circa 1920s (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Morrow, Jay (portraits), Circa 1925, 1928 (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Scandrett family, 1905, undated (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Friends, acquaintances, and others
    - [Alfort?], Dr., Circa 1860s-1870s (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Ford, Henry (portrait), Circa 1930 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Guggenheim, Diane, 1940s? (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Hauptman, Anna, Circa 1985 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Hearst, William Randolph, 1930s? (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Herrick, Myron T., Circa 1927 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Love, Phillip R., 1930s (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Marion, 1930s (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - [McCormick?], Robert N., 1930s? (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Smith, Colonel Truman, 1930s (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Spalding, Edward Bartlett, Circa 1950s (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Unidentified, Circa 1870s-1930s (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Graphic Art
      - Lindbergh, Anne Morrow
        - Drawings by, 1944, undated (Box 79, Folder 1)
        - Drawing for, Undated (Box 79, Folder 2)
        - Drawings of, 1922-circa 1950 (Box 79, Folder 3-5)
        - Painting by, 1939 (Box 79, Folder 6)
        - Painting by, Undated (Box 86, Folder 7)
      - Lindbergh, Charles Augustus
        - Drawings by, 1930s-1950s (Box 80, Folder 1-2)
          Includes book cover illustrations, a map, and mechanical/engineering drawings of pulsation pump and other devices.
        - Drawings by, 1938 March 13 (Box 86, Folder 8)
          Engineering drawing of perfusion pump.
        - Drawings of, 1927-1987 (Box 80, Folder 3-5)
        - Drawing of, Circa 1933 (Box 86, Folder 9)
        - Drawing and painting for, 1928, 1930 (Box 80, Folder 6)
        - Painting by, 1939 (Box 80, Folder 7)
        - Paintings of, Circa 1928 (Box 80, Folder 8)
        - Poster for, 1985 May 20-26 (Box 86, Folder 10)
          Advertising Lindbergh heritage week.
        - Scrapbook, 1927-1937 (Box 81)
          Illustrated scrapbook given (?) to Lindbergh commemorating the 1927 transatlantic flight.
      - Lindbergh children, drawings by, Circa 1940s (Box 82, Folder 1)
      - Lindbergh, Jon, drawing by Olaf Gulbransson, 1950? (Box 82, Folder 2)
      - Lindbergh, Land, painting by, Undated (Box 86, Folder 11)
      - Lindbergh, Evangeline Lodge Land
        - Painting by, Undated (Box 83, Folder 1)
        - Painting of, with Evangeline Lodge Land, Undated (Box 83, Folder 2)
        - Painting of, with Charles Henry Land, Jr., Undated (Box 83, Folder 3)
        - Miscellaneous artwork owned by? (Box 83, Folder 4)
        - Land, Charles H. (drawings by), 1900 (Box 83, Folder 5)
      - Morrow, Elizabeth Cutter, painting of, Undated (Box 84, Folder 1)
      - Morrow, Elisabeth Reeve, drawings and painting of, 1927-1933 (Box 84, Folder 2)
      - Topical-Airplanes, Undated (Box 84, Folder 3)
      - Miscellaneous drawing, Undated (Box 86, Folder 12)
      - Miscellaneous artwork and prints, Undated (Box 85, Folder 1-3)
  - Topical
    - Africa, Undated (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Arctic Circle--Fiala-Ziegler Polar Expedition, 1903-1905 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Arizona, 1929, undated (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - California, 1931 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Colorado, 1911 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Detroit, Michigan, 1898 (Box 86, Folder 1)
      Panoramic view published by the Detroit Journal.
    - Minnesota, Little Falls, Circa 1960s, Undated (Box 77, Folder 5)
      Little Falls.
    - Minnesota, Undated (Box 86, Folder 2)
      Panoramic postcard of Little Falls, Minnesota.
    - New York, 1927 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Washington, DC, 1913 March 4 (Box 86, Folder 3)
      Panoramic view of the United States Capitol building during the inauguration of President Wilson.
    - Unidentified places, Undated (Box 86, Folder 4)
      Panoramic view.
    - Spirit of St. Louis, 1927-1971 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Airplanes, Undated (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Consolidated Air Craft Corporation, 1936-1938 (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Flying cadets at Brooks Field, Texas, 1924 April (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - U.S. Commemorative Tour airplanes, 1927-1977 (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Unidentified airplanes, Undated (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Houses and buildings
      - Cutter house in Cleveland, Ohio (album), Undated (Box 78, Folder 1)
        Interior views.
      - Morrow family (?), Circa 1950s (Box 77, Folder 11)
      - Next Day Hill in New Jersey (album), Circa 1940s-1960s (Box 78, Folder 2)
      - Unidentified, Undated (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - Other items related to Charles and Anne Lindbergh, Undated (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Photographs, rolled (Box 102)